Breakfast is ready!
'Kay. Be there in a sec.
You're in an awfully good mood today.
Well, of course I am!
Today's the day my dream comes true!
Stream           Steam            Steam
Steam
Steam            Steam
I can't help but notice
you're working hard on your day off.
Try not to overdo—
I know.
I'll be home by dinnertime.
Alright, I'm heading out.
See ya later!
Well, guess I'd better get ready—
MAY!
What's the matter, Bell?
It's Hinata! He's...!
37.8°C.
Is he gonna die?! What should we do?!
If Hinata dies, I'll die, too!
You're being dramatic. I told you it's just a cold.
If Cecil were here, I'd have her cast a healing spell,
but she already left for work...
Okay, you wait here! I'll go get her right now!
We shouldn't bother her while she's working.
It's low-grade fever. I'll just take
some medicine and sleep it off.
But you ought to at least eat something...
Bell, why don't you make Hinata something
that'll be light on his stomach?
Light on his stomach...?
A rice porridge would probably be easiest.
I've never made anything like that before!
You should make it, May!
I'd like to, but I'm supposed to film
a collab video in a little while.
A collab?
Yup!
I get the chance to do my dream collaboration
with the magical girl idol trio
Defending World Peace
at All Costs
who inspired me to start streaming in the first place!
Do you even care what happens to Hinata?!
I-I do, but...
Bell, don't put her in a tough spot.
I'm happy for you, May.
Don't worry about me and go have fun.
Sorry, Hinata.
Bye! Hope you feel better!
Bell?
What is it, Hinata? What's wrong?
Is there something you need me to do?
It's just... It makes me nervous
when you hover over me like that...
F-Forgive me. I can't help but worry about you...
Are you sure you're alright? Wanna suck on my boobs?
N-No, I don't!
Hinata...?!
I'm sorry, I don't know how to help you. I'm totally lost...
I'm okay, I promise. It's not a big deal.
Well, for now, why don't you make Hinata
something that'll be light on his stomach?
Rice porridge...
Empty...
They're having a sale today,
so I figured I'd wait and buy everything at once...
Hinata! Should you be up right now?
It's fine. I'll go shopping once I'm feeling a little better.
Go lie back down.
Huh?
I'll go and get some groceries!
Ugh, work was rough...
Her figure is incredible. She a model?
Can't wait for the party today!
All these people's emotions... It's too much!
Huh? Bell?
Sakura...
You're alone? Where's Sunohara?
At home sick with a cold.
What? Oh no!
I decided to go shopping so
that I can make him rice porridge...
I made a list and everything,
but I don't know where to shop...
I can't do anything on my own...
Oh, Bell! It's going to be okay.
What do you need to buy? I'll help you.
Sakura...!
That's what friends are for, right?
Thank you!
I-I can't breathe, Bell!
H-How about you show me the list you made?
Maebara Rice Shop
It's heavy.
If you leave me your address,
I can deliver it to your front door.
Are you sure?
Of course, it would be my pleasure.
Welcome!
Oh? You're the young lady who's always with Sunohara.
He isn't with you today?
Um...
Sunohara's sick with a cold.
Oh, that's too bad. Here...
Take these with you.
Huh? But...
In times of need, we oughtta help each other out.
Thank you!
Is he asleep?
His fever's still high... He's sweating, too.
Bell, do you have a hot towel or something?
Wh-Where am I...?
You're in Heaven.
Huh? Bell?
Mochida?
Sunohara...
Just sit still. We're going to make you feel all better...
Bell...
Don't forget about me.
Are you sensitive here?
No fair. I want a turn!
S-Stop it! I can't get up!
Really...? But you got this part up just fine.
She's right. Impressive.
Now I want a taste...
I get to go first, right, Hinata?
Sunohara...
Hinata...
H-Hold on...
NO, WAIT—!
Huh? Wait, what...?
Sorry, did we wake you?
You were sweating like crazy.
H-Hi, Sunohara.
Mochida? You're here, too? But why?
Hinata, stay still.
B-Bell...
Feels like your fever went down a little.
Think you can eat?
Uh-huh...
Good. Then I'll go whip something up.
Sorry, Bell.
There's no need to apologize.
In fact, it makes me happy that I get to help you.
I'd gladly do anything so long as it benefits you.
Thanks for the food.
You gobbled that down quick, didn't you?
The fact that you've got an appetite means you're on
the mend.
Well, there's that, and... it was really tasty.
Nice going, Bell!
Couldn't have done it without your help, Sakura!
I wouldn't mind eating a meal like that every day!
Hinata! Don't tell me that was a... p-p-proposal?!
No, I just—!
If that's what you want, then I'll make it every day!
Cut it out, Bell! Not in front of Mochida!
This is perfect!
Hinata!
Hinata, you're sweating.
Oh, yeah. The rice porridge was warm, so...
I'll grab you a change of clothes,
so why don't you hop in the bath?
Alright, if you insist.
The water feels nice.
And I'm not so achy anymore...
Sunohara...
Just sit still. We're going to make you feel all better...
Jeez, talk about a wild dream...
Bell, come back here!
Let's bathe together!
You can't—!
C'mon, I'll scrub you down!
S-Sorry, Mochida!
I'm getting out now! You two enjoy the bath!
But Hinata...
I saw Sunohara naked...
This sucks. I wanted to take a bath with Hinata...
You really do love Hinata, don't you, Bell?
Of course. Remember what I told you?
Hinata and I were destined for each other.
Suhonara's a lucky guy, having someone
like you care so much about him.
Yeah? I hope so.
That reminds me. Do you like anyone, Sakura?
Huh? W-Well, I...
Judging by that face, you do!
What're they like?
He's sweet, and he's warm like sunshine,
and he goes out of his way to help others... I guess?
Huh... He sounds a lot like Hinata.
Have you told him?
N-No, I can't!
If you don't tell him, nothing will come of it.
Instead of just waiting around,
you've got to do something!
Do something, huh...
I can't believe Lord Hinata caught a cold.
Bell's never been very good at cooking.
I bet they're starving!
We're back!
How're you feeling, Hinata?
Welcome home.
I feel a whole lot better now.
I'm glad to hear it.
And who's this?
Oh, pardon my manners!
Sakura Mochida. I'm Sunohara's classmate.
Um, you're May, right?
Huh? Do I know you?
Um, actually, I've watched
every single one of your streams!
If you're a friend of Bell's, then that means you really are
from another world and it's not just a joke for the internet!
It's no wonder I felt like all the parallel world
stuff was so realistic!
Also, are your ears real?!
U-Um, if you don't mind, could I touch—
Sakura, take a breath.
A fan of May's videos?
Ask your questions one at a time, please. Slowly.
I-I'm sorry...
Ah, so fluffy!
That kinda tickles!
Oh, my bad!
It's okay. Just be a little more gentle, 'kay?
O-Okay!
This might be the most fun I've ever had.